Hello.
こんにちは
It's really cute.
め っちゃ可愛いですね
It feels fresh.
フレッシュな感じで
Wow, you're a famous person, aren't you?
すごい 有名人なんでしょ?
I have a lot of followers on Instagram.
ちょっとインスタのフォロワー多いくらいです
Is it a bit much?
ちょっと多い?
It's a bit much.
ちょっと多い
How many people?
何人くらいですか?
There are about 250,000 people now.
今25万人くらい
That's too many.
多すぎるね
It's not just a little bit.
ちょっとじゃないじゃん
Someone famous?
有 名な方?
I think she is quite famous among models.
モデルの中では結構有名な方だと思う
Is that so?
そうなの?
Are you a model?
モデルさんをやってる?
that's right.
そうです
I see.
なるほどね
It's an acceptable style.
納得のスタイルだね
What kind of activities do you usually do?
普段どういう活動をしたりしてるの?
It appears in a lot of magazines.
雑誌とか結構出てます
TV, etc.
テレビとかも
tv set?
テレビ?
TV or something.
テレビとか
That's right.
そうなんだ
You're such a celebrity.
めちゃくちゃ芸能人してるね
Is your job difficult?
大変ですか、仕事?
It's fun.
楽しいですよ
Although it can be difficult sometimes.
大変なこともありますけど
fun?
楽しい?
That's right.
そうなんだ
What was it that you originally dreamed of?
もともと何、そうなるの夢だったの?
I agree.
そうですね
I've been watching models on TV for a long time.
昔からテレビでモデルさんとか見てて
There were quite a few.
結構いました
That's right.
そうなんだ
Is there a celebrity you admire?
憧れの芸能人さんとかいる?
I'm here.
います
There are a few people though.
何人かですけど
For example, who?
例えば誰ですか?
For example, I'm just pulling back here.
例えば、ちょっとここでは引いてます
I can't say that.
それは言えないね
That's right.
そうなんだ
So, are you used to being taken like this?
じゃあ、こう取られたりするのは慣れてるかな?
Sorry, I'm turning things around so quickly.
ごめん、急に回しちゃってるけど
I agree.
そうですね
I'm pretty used to being taken.
取られること自体は結構慣れてます
I agree.
そうだね
That's the kind of job it is.
そういうお仕事だもんね
yes.
はい
He answered clearly and clearly, but
ちゃんとハキハキ答えてくれてるけど、
Suddenly.
いきなりね
Are you that naughty?
そんなヘッチなの?
There's no such thing as a hectic one, right?
ヘッチなのないでしょ?
No.
ないです
It's my first time.
初めてです
Hey.
ねえ
I just caught a glimpse of your body,
さ っき体チラッと見ちゃったけど、
It's such a great style.
すごいスタイルいいよね
thank you.
ありがとうございます
What about Gravia?
グラウィアとかは?
Do you wear swimsuits to work?
水着とか着て仕事?
It's not there anymore.
もうないですね
That kind of H type.
そういうH系の
H series.
H系の
There isn't.
ないんだ
yes.
はい
I see.
そ っか
Today, I thought I'd let you take a look at my body.
今日はちょっとね、体をね、ちょっと取らせてもらおうかなって
Are you interested in that?
そういうのが興味はあるの?
Haughty things.
ヘッチなこと
I'm a little interested.
ちょっと興味あります
ちょっと興味
Do you have a boyfriend?
彼氏とかいます?
No, it's not there.
いや、いないです
not present?
いない?
Work is more fun now.
今、お仕事の方が楽しいので
I see.
そっか
Work, I'm busy.
仕事ね、忙しいからね
Stay focused.
集中してね
Well, I'm sure it'll be popular.
まあ、モテるだろうけど
How many people have drawing experience?
絵経験人数とかは?
By the way.
ちなみに
There are only about 2 people.
2人くらいしかないです
Isn't that so?
それはそうでしょ
Normally.
普通に
2 people?
2人?
yes.
はい
oh dear,
まあ、
But is that it?
でも あれか
They are two well-chosen people.
ちゃんと選んだ2人なんだ
I agree.
そうですね
Chosen.
選ばれし
I think I'll take a look at some things today.
ちょっと今日いろいろ見ていこうかなって思いますね
People often say it's long.
よく長いって言われます
Because it's a model.
モデルなので
That's right.
そうだよね
This is so.
これはそうだ
It's amazing when you actually see it.
実際に見るとすごいね
It looks a little glimmering.
ちょっとチラチラ見える
Aren't you embarrassed?
恥ずかしくない?
Just a glimpse.
チラチラ見えるだけ
It's amazing, this one too.
すごいよね、こっちの方も
Aren't you a little nervous?
ちょっと緊張してるんじゃない?
I'm nervous.
緊張してます
Why is it my first time?
初めてなんで
That's right.
そうだよね
Your legs are long.
長いよ、足を
Well, I don't really see models' feet.
ちょっと、モデルさんの足見るのあんまないんで
It smells like raspberry.
ラズベリニーの香りだって
I don't do that much.
そんなにしません
Hey, hey,
ちょっと、ちょっと、
That's it.
そんな
Like that, like that.
そんな、 そんな
It's a foot.
足です
I've been bullied before.
いじめたことある
Isn't there?
ないですか?
Is that how you feel?
そんな感じですか?
This is better.
こっちの方がいい
Do you understand that?
そういうの分かる?
I wondered if there was anything I could do with my feet.
足でできることはないかなって
I have no idea.
全然分からない
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
It's long.
長いね
Is it long?
長いですか?
Wow, right away.
すごい、すぐ
I'm going to touch it right away, that kind of thing.
すぐ触っちゃうの、そんな
Because it's from above.
上からだから
From above?
上から?
OK from above.
上からOK
It's a person.
人です
Super cute.
超可愛い
It's getting a little tight.
ちょっと締めてきてる
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Pull it out to the side and see this.
横に抜いてみて、これ
It's completely visible.
丸見えだよ
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
First of all, it's a bit studio-heavy.
ちょっと、スタジオの濃いね、まず
That's about it.
これくらい
I can't see it at all.
全然ちょっと見えない
It's a little hot, isn't it?
ちょっと暑いでしょ?
It's hot.
暑いね
Go to sleep, then.
寝るか、じゃあ
Were you sleeping?
寝てた?
amazing.
すごい
Time too.
タイムも
Were you dressed like that?
そんな格好してたの?
Erotic
エロ
Yes.
い ね
She looks erotic.
エロい格好してる
I like the style.
すげースタイルいいね
Well, that's true.
まあ、そりゃそうなんだけどね
It's a temple.
お寺さんだもんね
You can drink this forever.
ずっと飲めちゃうね、これね
Hey, turn your butt back.
ちょっとこう、お尻、後ろ向いて
hey.
ね
Just a little help.
ちょっと 手ついてさ
Please turn around for a moment.
ちょっとこっち振り向いてみてね
Erotic.
エロい
You're looking good.
いい格好してるじゃん
Wow, that crack.
すごい、割れ目が
I want to do what I like, right?
好きなのしたいよね、これ
is that so?
そうですか?
I love the cracks though.
割れ目が好き好きだけど
Did you know?
知ってた?
I didn't know.
知らなかった
I didn't know, did you know?
知らないで、知ってたの?
I don't understand that.
そんなわからん
difficult.
難しい
Don't you know?
知ってないの?
It's getting soggy.
グシュグシュになってる
You're beautiful, oppa.
綺麗だな、おっぱ
stomach.
い
That's great.
す げーいいね
Delicious breasts.
おいしい、おっぱい
It's soft.
柔らかいね
tiger
トラ
Are you excited about the bar?
バ ルって興奮してるの?
Yeah.
うん
difficult.
難しい
difficult?
難しい?
Ah, amazing.
あ、すごい
Shy.
恥ずかしがって
Wow, that's good.
すっごい、いいでしょ
Choo Choo Modulu.
チューチューモジュルー
It feels good.
気持ちいいな
Feels good.
気持ちいい
You like dick, right?
チンチン好きでしょ?
I like it.
好きです
My body isn't feeling well.
身体はっきりいこいないから
Ching Chin, just a moment.
チンチン、ちょっと
Isn't it painful?
痛いんじゃない?
Ah, good at it.
あー、上手
You're good at it.
上手だね
Amazing, so good.
すごい、上手
That's amazing.
すごいね
Just a little bit,
ちょっとさ、
Breasts, breasts like this,
お っぱいさ、 おっぱいでこうさ、
Try pinching this.
挟んでみて、これ
Oh yeah, yeah.
そうそう、そう
Squeeze it between your breasts.
挟んでさ、 おっぱいする
Pinch it on both sides.
両サイドで挟む
What do you think?
どうだいでしょ?
No.
ないです
That's amazing.
すごいね
Are you having sex?
エッチョしてるの?
Haven't you?
してないの?
I haven't.
してないです
for a while.
しばらく
Is it impossible for a while?
しばらく無理?
It won't be possible for a while.
しばらく無理です
Something hurt.
何かがつった
picture?
え?
what?
何?
I would like it to have rubber.
ゴムをつけて欲しいです
What, rubber?
え、ゴムを?
What is it?
なんだよ
Have you never done that before?
あんまでしたことないの?
I've never done it.
したことない
it's okay.
大丈夫だよ
It feels good.
気持ちいいよ
Don't be fooled by game activities or anything like that.
ゲームの活動とか、 ニジンしたらいけない
It's okay, I won't make a fuss.
大丈夫、ニジンしないって
But activities.
でも、活動とか
You had sex, right?
エッチしたでしょ?
Are you scared?
怖いの?
It's scary.
怖いです
Just a little bit is fine.
ちょっとだけいいじゃん
No.
ダメです
Seriously?
マジで?
Well, let's put it on.
じゃあ、つけようか
It's scary.
怖いもんね
Is there any?
あるかな?
I don't usually open it much.
普段、めっちゃ開いてないけどね
Because I don't wear it.
つけないからさ
Not wearing it is the worst.
つけないの最低な
The nails.
爪が
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
Nails?
爪が?
Because it's a little long.
ちょっと長いから
You know how to put it on.
つけ方ちょっと分かるよね
I don't like it.
嫌いね
Always wear it properly.
ちゃんとつけるの、いつも
Yes, I always wear it.
いつもつけてはい
An ex-boyfriend or something.
元彼とか
Just this.
ちょっと これで
It's okay.
大丈夫 ですよ
Very beautiful.
すごくキレイ
I'm coming here.
ここに来るんだよ
Feels good.
気持ちよい
what?
何?
Claimed to mention.
自称提起
I want to do color.
色をしたいんだよ
Would you like to try showing off once?
一回、出し映えしてみる?
Doesn't it feel good?
気持ちよいっしょ?
Ma
マ
N Juru.
ン ジュルが
It's pretty open.
結構開かれちゃってるね
Can I hang my breasts?
おっぱい掛けていい?
I'll hang my boobs like this.
こんな感じでおっぱい掛けるよ
Manjul.
マンジュルが
Let's go talk to me.
私を話しに行こうし
Okay, shall we go?
よし、行ってみる?
Yeah.
うん